(Decision to Start Anew)
Nice to see you all.
Anyway, our guest loves using the airfryer.
- The airfryer? - He's a bread maniac.
It's been a while, Bum June.
Nice to see you, everyone.
(Whenever he eats bread, )
(he smiles brightly.)
(This bread lover had bread almost for all of his meals.)
(- He's a serious bread lover. - What a precious guy he is.)
(He captured the hearts of bread lovers nationwide.)
- After my episode aired... - I bet it was crazy.
Yes. A lot of people reached out to me about tips...
on how to enjoy bread better.
He ate them with such great gusto.
- Okay. - I ordered bread...
while watching your episode on TV.
I love one of your famous memes.
The meme where you said, "I love cheese."
(I love cheese.)
- Let's eat bread together. - Seriously. Let's do it.
(We're clicking so well. Let's grab some bread sometime.)
(Feeling proud)
(Run, Hwani)
- "Run, Hwani." - "Run."
- "Hwani." - Why is he "Hwani?"
(Sung Hwan is walking somewhere, not running.)
He's wearing a cool outfit.
Did you film that right before you came here?
Gosh, no.
I thought you had stepped out of the screen.
His gloves stand out in the outfit.
They are my favorite gloves.
(He's going somewhere, dressed in a cool outfit.)
I wonder where he's going.
Gosh, there are a lot of motorcycles here.
- The street is filled with them. - What?
I know this place.
Here I am.
The bike street.
It's a motorcycle paradise.
I didn't know there was a street for them.
Right. That's a famous street.
- It's number 1 street for bikes. - It is number 1 street.
(Justifiably so, it offers a wide variety of motorcycles.)
The motorcycle street on Toegye-ro...
has the biggest motorcycle shops in Korea.
It's the street with all kinds of motorcycle shops.
It's a historical street.
I used to ride an electric bicycle.
- With Kkotbun. - With Kkotbun.
I mean, I love motorcycles.
But it's the childhood dream for most men.
A lot of men have a dream about riding motorcycles.
You know the motorcycle Jung Woo Sung from "Beat" rode?
- It's a CBR600F. - CBR600F. My gosh. That's...
Growing up, there was an American TV show...
called "Renegade."
"Renegade?"
- On the show... - That motorcycle suits you better.
He rode a cool motorcycle from Harley-Davidson.
Gosh, those motorcycles look so cool.
I've only seen motorcycles with raised handles.
I always dreamed of riding a motorcycle.
If I see a motorcycle I like today,
I'm going to buy it.
- It'd be a big decision, though. - He wants to buy one.
I went to the motorcycle street on Toegye-ro.
I bought one last year on Toegye-ro too.
- You bought another one? - Yes, last year.
You're switching to a better-performing model, right?
- You... - That's not my main focus.
I look at the design and the vibe.
- The vibe? - It's mainly about the vibe.
- Cars can't scratch this itch. - There's something about them.
- It's the sense of liberation. - People often mentioned that.
So when I travel, I rent a motorcycle.
Gosh, you can't say...
- you've lived a life... - I agree.
- without that experience. - It sounds like you're on it now.
This is how you must've felt when I talked about bread.
You have zero interests in this, right?
I know nothing about motorcycles. So it's...
We felt just like that when you talked about bread.
- So... - We didn't understand you.
(You can't eat it right away after airfrying it.)
(What does he mean by that?)
While listening to them, I thought,
"This is how they must've felt when I talked about bread."
- Yes, it's mirror therapy. - Right.
Our show is a blend of all our interests.
- Right. - For the first time...
- You're so right. That's it. - My gosh.
It's all about mixing our interests.
You understood the agenda of our show after ten years.
- After ten years. - It offers a variety of genres.
We offer variety.
(Browsing a variety of motorcycles)
This one looks good.
Hello, sir.
I'm here to look at some motorcycles.
- Sure. Go ahead. - Thanks.
You have a wide variety of motorcycles.
Right.
(The shop is full of various motorcycles.)
That's a lot.
Shops these days have a wider range of options.
There are more brands to choose from too.
- Most of them are used. - I see. They're used.
Most of them are used.
(There are all kinds of models too.)
- I'm here to buy a motorcycle. - Okay.
- Do you know the old movie, "Beat?" - Yes.
Jung Woo Sung rode a motorcycle in it.
It was called a CBR. It's the one...
- where you have to hunch over. - Yes.
This is the kind of motorcycle I want.
- This one. - That's your style.
- S 1000. - You're spot on.
- That one is cool. - Oh, that one.
Can I try sitting on it? I'll be gentle.
- Sure. - Gosh, I love it.
You're still young. You like motorcycles with higher seats.
- Yes, I like those motorcycles. - I'm scared to ride them.
It's been my dream.
(He excitedly puts on the helmet.)
(He's about to make his dream come true.)
Okay.
(Amazed)
The size was perfect. You see?
The handlebars look quite far away.
They are. That's why they have to hunch over.
My gosh. I'm getting goosebumps.
Really?
(He's making the sound orally.)
(Vroom)
(Back in the day, every motorcyclist wanted to recreate this scene.)
(Why don't you give it a try?)
(Like this?)
It feels great.
- That's the fast track to death. - It is.
- He'll meet the Jade Emperor. - The Jade Emperor.
A high-five.
I love it.
- I'll keep this one for now. - Okay.
Can you tell me how much this one costs?
It's going for 18,500 dollars.
- It's going for 18,500 dollars? - Yes.
- This one... - It's quite expensive.
- It's expensive. - Of course.
You were so excited like a little kid.
- But kids can't afford that. - Right. That's expensive.
- It's way too expensive. - His facial expression changed.
Right.
When was this manufactured?
In 2022.
- That was pretty recent. - Right.
- Does it go fast? - Yes, it goes really fast.
What's the maximum speed?
- Over 200km per hour. - Over 200?
Yes.
(He can't stop looking at the motorcycle.)
- I can't stop looking at it. - That's a great color scheme.
It is. I really liked the color scheme too.
But if you want to ride the motorcycle from BMW...
Do people say middle-tier?
- Yes, middle-tier. - You should try riding that first.
- Then move up to a bigger engine. - But riding that first...
- If you skip this step, - Is it too dangerous?
- people say it's dangerous. - It's dangerous.
- Right. - The thing is,
- they're super powerful. - Right. They're so powerful.
You must learn to control them.
You must listen to an experienced motorcyclist.
- Right. That's Kian84. - Yes. Listen to him.
- Can I listen to the engine? - Sure.
Okay.
My gosh. That's amazing.
(Getting a thrill)
(The engine lets out a satisfying roar.)
- Gosh, I see steam coming out. - That's amazing.
It's no joke when you listen to it in person.
- It gets your heart racing. - Yes.
- It's like rock music. - Really?
Gosh, this is different.
- Right. - Actually, I haven't...
The thing is... How should I go about this?
- Do you not have money saved up? - Well,
- I haven't... - A beginner-friendly one?
- No. The license... - You want to get the Class Two...
Small Motorcycle License and ride something for a beginner?
I haven't gotten the license yet.
- You haven't? - No, not yet.
No license? Hey!
- What are you doing then? - You went there first?
You don't even have a license?
What do you want the owner to do then?
Don't bring up the license in front of Lee Jung.
- I haven't healed from it yet. - Right.
- I'm still heartbroken about it. - I'm sorry, Jung.
- No. - That's why I'm avoiding your eyes.
I feel bad.
I have Class 1 Regular and Large Vehicle Licenses.
They are the only licenses I have, so I'll get the Class Two License.
I signed up to the test last week.
I'm going to take the test today at 3:30pm.
- You sound confident. - Right.
- That was my third time. - Okay.
- It was your 3rd time? - Yes, my 3rd time.
- Yes, my third time. - You already failed twice?
- So you failed twice? - You failed?
- I failed twice. That was... - That was your third time?
- That was my third time. - Did you fail the driving test?
- Yes, the driving skills test. - You failed the skills test?
- It's okay to fail a few times. - Right.
(He hears the voice of a savior when he's flustered.)
- Well... - Right.
- Jung. - Yes.
- Failing the test... - It happens to everyone.
- People fail tests, don't they? - It's a test.
You're disqualified.
The license for the motorcycles is really hard.
It's really hard.
I have the license for it.
- You do? - I have the Class Two License.
- You... - I passed it on my first try.
- What about you, Kian84? - I passed it on my 1st try.
My gosh. Really?
That's impressive.
I thought I'd pass it today.
- I see. - So I came before my test.
It won't take long for you to get it.
Looking at my build and physical traits...
- You're the expert. - Okay.
Which motorcycle would you recommend?
An American-style motorcycle would be good too.
- That one? - Yes.
That's catching my eyes too.
- I think that suits you better. - That suits you better.
Here I go.
- What do you think? - You look great.
- Which one is better? - That one is better for you.
- It is? - Yes.
That one looks great.
Okay.
(He rode two motorcycles before getting his license.)
- The license is the most important. - Yes.
That's why I went to look at some motorcycles that day.
I needed to have my eyes on a couple of motorcycles.
So they would motivate me.
- That way, I'd have a goal. - That's true. Like losing weight.
Yes. That's why. That's the perfect example.
Trying to lose weight...
- after buying a small outfit? - Yes.
You don't get to wear it in the end.
(Feeling guilty)
- You have good energy, right? - Yes.
Give me some good energy of a lucky motorcyclist.
Pass it and come back.
My gosh. You can count it.
- I'll come back at all costs. - Okay.
- This is my third time. - Yes.
- Let's not waste our breath on it. - Okay.
- Sir, see you later. - Okay.
Nothing could've motivated him more than that.
- I'm feeling great. - Bye.
I think he can pass it.
He looks confident.
My gosh. It's freezing.
It was freezing that day.
Gosh, it's cold.
It's way too cold.
(Fidgeting)
(Putting on the helmet when he has no motorcycle)
Put it on. That keeps you warm.
It's warm now.
It's warm.
My ears are warm.
It was really warm, by the way.
- This is... - You know what?
It looks like someone stole his motorcycle.
- I see. So... - So it's gone?
You'd ride the bicycle to school, but walk back home.
- I see. Because someone stole it? - Yes.
"My motorcycle."
My gosh. Seriously.
Hold on.
(Tapping)
(Let me see.)
Jongno.
I'm in Jongno now.
Jongno...
- What's that? - The list of good restaurants.
I have many folders of restaurants I frequent...
sorted by area on my phone.
Gangnam. Gangdong.
Jongno. There are many areas.
People ask me to share them, but I rarely do because...
I don't want the restaurants to get packed.
You've been to all of these restaurants.
Of course. I've been to all of them.
So you've been to 50 to 60 restaurants just in Jongno?
The Jongno Folder has more than 50 or 60 restaurants.
You must go to a lot of restaurants.
You can't even buy that kind of information...
- with money. - Right.
(Feeling proud)
(Where should I go today?)
Yes. I should go there.
(I should go there.)
Nice. This is great.
- It's a pasta restaurant? - No.
(Smiling from ear to ear)
Here I am.
My love, Zia.
Venezia.
Gosh, it's freezing.
It's so cold!
(A western-cuisine restaurant)
Look at the sign! Oh, my.
Western-cuisine restaurants...
- all have the same decor. - Right.
But this restaurant is the real deal.
It's so cold.
(He walks down to the basement.)
Hello.
It's been a while.
- Gosh. - How nice.
(The old-school decor everyone still remembers)
It's like a scene from a movie.
So many group blind dates...
- took place there. - The red bricks.
A lot of families dined out at restaurants like this.
Jongno still preserves the scenery of the past.
In my opinion, it gives us the nostalgic vibe.
I have many memories from here too.
As for this restaurant, it opened 39 years ago.
- My gosh. - Upon walking in,
you see all these interior props...
and feel the old vibe with the lights and all.
It's taking a trip down memory lane.
People come to eat here for romance and the vibe.
It's one of my favorite restaurants.
Sung Hwan really likes that.
- He loves romance. - It's really nice. I do.
Have you two been to a place like that yet?
Actually, do you know this restaurant in Jamsil?
It's called House of Pork Cutlets.
My gosh, I love that place.
I love that restaurant. You have to order...
two rolls of bread and one bowl of rice at the restaurant.
They bake their own bread. Their bread is so good.
- You go there for the bread. - For the pork cutlet. No.
They butter the rolls and give you apple jam on the side.
Have the roll plain with the jam.
- Then put... - Right.
Right. Put the pork cutlet and the salad in the roll.
I mix the rice with the leftover sauce at the end.
You order the pork cutlet set. Then you get...
I also order that. You get three pieces.
- I always get the assortment. - Fried fish, hamburger steak,
- and pork cutlet. - Yes.
Do you know this restaurant called Dolmen Pork Cutlet in Songpa?
My gosh. It's on my list.
But that place doesn't offer the assortment set.
- Right. - They only serve pork cutlets.
- And they give you udon. - It comes with the udon.
- That's right. - That's how I remember.
You guys seem to know the history of all these restaurants.
It's like elementary school kids memorizing subway stations.
You sound like a writer for a food column.
It feels like I've met my soulmate.
It's amazing how they memorized all this.
- Right. - Write about restaurants' history.
- Seriously. - But the thing is...
- You have the palate of a kid. - I do have the palate of a kid.
There's a dish you don't eat.
- I can't eat fermented skate. - Right.
There's an amazing restaurant for skate combo in my neighborhood.
The owner makes the wraps for you.
Hey, I know that place.
Right!
- Where? - How did you know?
- That place is super famous. - Where is that?
- The restaurant owner... - Where?
Makes every wrap for you.
So you just have to open your mouth.
That's the best restaurant for beginners.
That has to be the first restaurant to keep eating skate.
- Sung Hwan. - It sounds like...
he can eat everything.
(They're soulmates starting today.)
Whenever I come here,
it feels like I'm traveling to the past on a time machine.
Sir.
Could I have the menu?
Thank you.
(Even the menu looks old-school.)
The menu itself has an old-school vibe.
He's busy.
- Sir. - Yes.
I'd like the pork cutlet...
and the fish cutlet.
(He's on his phone again after placing the order.)
(Playing the practice video for the driving test)
That's a difficult part.
(He grabs invisible handlebars and moves his hands around.)
Right. Visualizing it in your head...
- is quite helpful. - It helps a lot.
Turn. One and two.
(While he's determined to pass the test...)
Thank you.
Are you taking a test today?
Yes. I'm taking the test for the motorcycle license.
- I'll pray for you. - So... Thank you.
I just have to make sure I don't get nervous.
Don't be nervous.
My heart is pounding even right now.
- So... - I'm sure you'll pass it.
That's why I came to my favorite restaurant.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
He's getting a lot of good energy.
That's right.
(It instantly brings back old memories.)
That looks good.
Look at that.
(Western-style fish cutlet and pork cutlet)
This place looks good.
You can't have the western pork cutlet without radish kimchi.
(It comes with radish kimchi and pickled radish.)
- Thank you. - Here's the dessert.
Thank you. My gosh.
He even cut the apples into shapes.
- Isn't that so romantic? - Yes.
Check out the toothpick wrapped with cellophane sheets.
- The toothpick. - Look at that toothpick.
- I haven't seen them in ages. - It's been forever.
The toothpick with cellophane sheets.
(After a brief reminder of the old days, )
(he slices the cutlet.)
(Amazed)
That's a nice feeling.
Seeing how the knife is going in nicely, I'll pass the test.
- That looks so good. - That does look good.
"You'll pass."
(He cuts the cutlet while wishing to pass the test.)
I cut everything at once.
So I can keep eating.
- So you don't have to pause? - Right, no pause.
(He picks up a piece of the pork cutlet and eats it.)
(Humming)
Fried food tastes good in general.
Even fried shoes would taste good.
- Right. - Yes.
(This time, he picks up the fish cutlet.)
- The fish cutlet looks good. - Their fish cutlet is good.
(Staring)
- You're keeping the balance. - Of course.
- You go back and forth. - I have to alternate.
I have a long list of great restaurants.
Let's check out a few.
- Sounds good. - He likes to eat. Great.
(Savoring the dishes while alternating between them)
It's good.
(Sighing)
I must have only positive thoughts.
(He has another bite while trying to be positive.)
(He swallows his anxiety with the pork cutlet.)
I already finished everything.
You ate everything.
- That's impressive. - That's...
Now that I had your lovely pork cutlet...
and fish cutlet,
I'll come back with my license.
- I'll come back on a motorcycle. - Sure.
I'll say goodbye here.
Sure. My gosh.
Bye.
- Did you enjoy the food? - Yes. I always enjoy your food.
Our restaurant spreads good luck.
- Right. - I'm sure you'll have a lucky day.
How romantic.
She always says the sweetest things.
Thank you.
- Have a good day. - Thank you for coming.
- I have a good feeling about this. - All right. Thank you.
I bet you passed because you ate there.
If you hadn't, you probably didn't pass.
He must pass the test for the restaurant to do well.
If you fail, you should go back and apologize.
(Now that I got some good energy, let's go and pass the test.)
Let's go.
Thank you.
(A taxi arrives at that moment.)
- Hello. - Hello.
I'm actually taking the test for my license.
- I see. - It's the motorcycle license.
I see.
I'm getting nervous.
(Nervous and anxious)
I haven't felt this nervous in a while.
Sir, is there a way to relax when you get nervous?
Is the test that difficult to pass?
Gosh, it's no joke.
On my 1st try, about 13 people signed up.
- Only two people passed. - Right.
- Really? - It's really hard.
I used to ride an MX125 back in the day.
Where?
You met a cool taxi driver.
I lived in Sillim-dong back then.
You couldn't see me apart from the motorcycle.
I had to hunch over a lot.
I didn't know you used to ride an MX125.
- Yes. I rode an MX125. - It's every man's dream.
All men have this dream.
They dream of riding motorcycles.
Everyone carries a sense of romance at heart.
I almost died three times.
- My gosh. - Yes.
I can't ride that anymore because I'm scared.
Right. People need to be aware of the danger.
They must be careful when they're on motorcycles.
- You can't go back after accidents. - Right.
There's something about you.
That's why everyone tells anyone with a motorcycle to be careful.
There's a reason for it.
Looking at your hairstyle, I can tell you had a wild past.
Your hairstyle reminds me...
- of Tony Leung. - Right.
It's my first time having this much fun...
while driving a passenger.
My gosh. This is great. I love talking to you.
- What a relief. - I don't feel nervous anymore...
after talking to you.
I'm almost 100 percent sure that I'll pass today.
- Thank you. - Sure.
(They arrive at the destination as they enjoy chatting.)
- Sir, can I shake your hand? - My gosh. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- I'll make sure to pass. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(I have a good feeling about today.)
(Looking around)
(Seoul Western Motorcycle Training Center)
A training center for motorcycles?
That's an indoor training center.
Gosh, I didn't know there was a training center.
It's a training center where you can practice...
your driving skills for the Class Two License.
I came here to practice my skills for the second time.
(It's full of training motorcycles.)
The test for the Class Two Small Motorcycle License...
has four parts.
I'd give anything to skip the first part.
It's the curved course.
That's the worst part.
- There are two curved turns. - That looks hard.
- Many people fail at that part. - Yes, a lot of people do.
The second part is the S-curve course.
The course is S-shaped.
- That's more doable than you think. - It's doable.
For the third part, I have to go straight...
- That one is hard too. - on a narrow street.
- What? What's this? - You must pick up the speed here.
That's the hard part.
Lastly, for the fourth part,
- I must drive in a zigzag pattern. - You can't fail that part.
Then you shouldn't be on a motorcycle.
Once I pass all four parts,
I'll get this beautiful license for motorcycles.
You're allowed to go off course once on this test.
But starting with the second time, you're disqualified.
Here you go.
(Checking his driver's license)
(I'll pass no matter what today.)
(He's ready to practice his driving skills.)
- You're practicing on your own? - You must be cold.
- That's why I watched... - Oh, my.
A lot of practice videos at the restaurant.
It's freezing.
(Let me go for a ride now.)
I'm nervous.
(Mounting the motorcycle with excitement)
- It's a matter of mentality. - That's right.
- It's a matter of mentality. - Let's not be nervous.
All set.
(Revving up)
(Full of excitement)
Sung Hwan, you look cool.
(He carefully moves to the starting point.)
(Raising his hand)
They call your name.
When they say, "Ku Sung Hwan," I raise my hand and begin.
(Nervous)
Cornering is the most important.
Watching him makes me nervous.
- I know. - There are lines on the floor.
- He crossed the lines. - Gosh.
He crossed the lines.
(He deviates from the track from the start.)
(The motorcycle shakes like his mentality.)
(He'll fail the test if he crosses the lines twice.)
For goodness' sake.
- Oh, no. - What happened?
- Scores will get deducted. - Oh, no.
- Did he cross the lines again? - This won't do.
It wasn't easy to avoid crossing the lines.
- Start over. - You fail if you do it twice.
- You fail. - You fail.
I'm bad at cornering.
The curved course...
is the most important in the motorcycle license test.
It's the first course you encounter.
Once you pass the curved course,
there's a 95 percent chance you'll pass.
- That's right. - So that's the hard part.
I failed the last two times because of the curved course.
(Most people fail at the curved course.)
I'm having a third attempt in order to get some practice.
The speed is important.
You can't go slow.
You fall if you go slow.
- You lose your balance and fall. - You lose your balance.
That's the difficult part.
- That's the worst course. - Yes.
The hardest course is in the beginning.
- That's right. - That's where everyone fails.
- That's right. - I did that two times.
Back in my days, 6 out of 10 people failed.
- Really? - Yes.
It's much harder than driving a car.
- It looks hard. - It looks so hard.
- Other courses are doable. - Yes.
(I'll succeed in it this time.)
- For goodness' sake. - Why are you going so fast?
- Why do you keep... - You're going too fast.
- Why are you getting angry? - I mean...
- You lack the talent. - It happens.
Why are you getting angry?
- I... - Just quit it.
- Already? - You lack the talent.
- Just eat pork cutlet. - Why are you getting angry?
Who drives that fast?
Drive a mini car with Ju Seung.
What are you talking about? I want to ride a motorcycle.
For goodness' sake.
(Sad)
(He continues to practice.)
- Why are you going so fast? - For goodness' sake.
No. It's okay.
- He's going too fast. - Slow down.
- Slow down! - He's really bad at this.
This is so frustrating.
I think he should get some help.
- That's right. - I know.
(What?)
What's this?
- Someone came. - Who's that?
Someone came.
- Who's that? - It's an indoor training center.
Is that Jong Hyuk?
- It's an indoor training center. - Yes.
(Jun Su, what's your dad's name?)
(Lee Jong Hyuk)
He's all grown up now.
(As Jun Su's dad, )
(he became the national dad.)
- How cute. - He looks so cute.
(Sung Hwan's close friend, Actor Lee Jong Hyuk)
Jun Su and Tak Su's dad, Jong Hyuk came.
He said he had the Class Two Small Motorcycle License.
He said that he was a motorcycle expert.
So I asked him for help.
There are many options.
- An instructor came. - Now...
- I heard that you failed twice. - Today, I'll have my third test.
When you failed twice,
- did you practice alone? - I practiced alone.
I practiced alone and watched YouTube videos.
- Didn't you attend an academy? - No. I did everything on my own.
It's no wonder you failed the test.
So I wanted to learn from you.
Please take a look...
- as I drive. - Okay.
Please tell me what I'm doing wrong.
The fact that you're trying anything is wrong.
He's a nagger.
Don't joke around. I'm nervous about the test.
Of course, you're nervous.
Hey, you're going too fast.
- I begin here. - I told you that you were fast.
- I told you that you were fast. - He noticed right away.
(Raising his hand)
- What are you doing? - They'll call my name.
I'm keeping everything the same for the simulation.
- Okay. Go ahead. - He only does that well.
- Go. - Oh, no.
- I... - You failed.
- You fail if you do that. - I told you that I was nervous.
Why did you yell "Go" so loudly?
(He keeps everything the same for the simulation.)
Won't he succeed in it right away since the instructor is there?
- Go slowly. - Let's go.
Look far ahead.
You crossed the lines.
(He crosses the lines this time as well.)
Keep going.
- Did I cross the lines? - Yes, you did.
- Even now? - I think so.
You failed.
I think you're going too fast.
- Am I going too fast? - Yes.
Step on the brakes as you go.
Give me a demonstration.
- Me? - Yes. I can't get...
a sense of it when I ride the motorcycle myself.
Just show me how you pass the first course.
(The motorcycle expert decides to give...)
(a demonstration.)
- Here I go. - Go ahead.
- I'll show you how to do it. - Okay. Show me.
Wouldn't he do it with ease?
He'd pass the test at once.
(Shouting)
What?
(Staggering)
- What's going on? - Where is he going?
Hey.
(Jun Su's dad, where are you going?)
- I mean... - What are you doing?
I think I'll fail the test.
(He turns off the engine.)
What are you doing?
(Embarrassed)
Please watch me from the back as I ride the motorcycle.
(He goes back to practicing before he loses the hang of it.)
Slowly.
Now, turn.
- He did it. - Nice.
- Well done. - It was so smooth.
Now, turn.
- There you go. It's okay. - Good.
- Does that get a pass? - That gets a pass.
- Finally, he'll pass. - Good.
Jong Hyuk, I got the hang of it.
Try it one more time.
That's it. Good. That's smooth.
I suddenly got the hang of it as if I was riding a bicycle.
That's smooth. Good.
(Laughing)
I got the hang of it.
That's good. You're good at riding a motorcycle.
- Look at this. I'm all set. - There you go.
- I'm all set. There's nothing more. - There you go.
That's good.
After Jong Hyuk came,
my driving improved a lot.
In soccer, being a soccer player...
and being a coach are two different things.
I think Jong Hyuk does better as a coach than a field player.
That's right. Not all coaches are good at soccer.
- I'll get going now. - Okay.
- Do another round before the test. - Okay.
- I'll say goodbye from here. - Okay.
All right. I'm all set.
It's a good weather to ride a motorcycle.
Hello. All right.
You need to take the test when you get the hang of it.
That's right. You need to take it right away.
(Singing a tune)
(Korea Road Traffic Authority, Seobu Examination Office)
(The location of the final battle)
I think I got my license there.
Most people do.
I think I saw this place...
- when Lee Jung crossed the road. - That's right.
You need to step on the yellow lines only.
- Why? - I came up with that rule.
- Hold on. - But you failed the test.
Yes.
(I'll overcome the jinxes.)
(Test registration)
I remember getting my license.
It was so nerve-racking.
(He can't hide how nervous he is.)
- You can go right away. - Okay. Thank you.
(He heads over to take the driving test.)
(Driving test center for small motorcycles)
(He arrives at the waiting room of the driving test center.)
Why is no one here?
(Rummaging)
(Sighing)
Now,
people are arriving one at a time.
(The test takers enter.)
(Staring)
Is it your first driving test?
(Is it your first driving test?)
- Yes. - Do you know him?
No. I've never met him before.
(He sits next to Sung Hwan.)
How many times...
have you taken the driving test?
This is my first time.
It's your first time. Have you practiced?
No, I'm a strong man who doesn't need to practice.
This has nothing to do with being a strong man.
- Didn't you practice at all? - No, I didn't.
Really?
Then the courses...
I'm sure they're all the same.
I just need to follow them.
I don't know if he'll do well or badly.
But... Really?
If I fail, I'll take the test again.
(So cool)
- He's very cool about it. - He has a good idea.
He's a manly man.
(The test taker is easygoing.)
Do you know how to ride a motorcycle?
- Yes, I have a moped license. - You have a moped license.
I bet he rode 125cc motorcycles.
I think he'll pass.
I'll pass in one go.
In one go?
- He has so much confidence... - Totally.
- even though it's his first try. - Yes.
Let's stay positive.
Let's do it.
Is there a motorcycle you want to buy...
after getting a license?
I want the 2008 model of CBR600RR.
That's incredible. I checked out CBR today.
- You have a good taste. - Let's get CBR. Seriously.
Let's get CBR. Seriously.
Is he someone you know?
- You guys get along so well. - No.
(They get along as they've always been friends.)
Where do you live, brother?
I live in Gangnam-gu.
- Gangnam-gu? - Yes.
- Alone or... - I live with my mom.
Gosh, you're from the district with the best education.
I might not look it, but I'm a filial son.
I pay for rent.
I got a job at the age of 20.
I work as a car mechanic.
- In what year were you born? - I was born in 2006.
- Did he say 2006? - He's a baby.
Brother, let's introduce each other.
My name is Park Tae Hwan.
- I'm 21 years old. - Park Tae Hwan.
Yes.
I'm Ku Sung Hwan.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- Both names end with Hwan. - Hwan.
We'll pass thanks to the good energy.
We'll pass no matter what. It's bound to happen.
- If you pass... - Okay.
Let's exchange numbers...
so that we can enjoy a ride together.
That sounds good. I'm honored.
Please give me your number.
I'll go home and brag about what happened.
It's an honor for the entire family.
Don't I have a good number?
Yes, you do.
Tae Hwan, thank you.
I'm becoming less nervous.
That's good to hear.
I'm glad to help.
Where do you want to go for a ride?
Me? I want to go to the Namhansanseong Fortress.
Why? To eat boiled chicken?
While boiled chicken is nice,
I like speeding.
Paldang is a great destination.
- Paldang? - Let's go to Paldang.
How much can you eat?
How many packets of ramyeon can you eat?
- I can eat five packets. - Really?
I eat more than I look.
Do you mean it? Don't overestimate yourself.
- I eat a lot. - I eat a lot too.
Okay. Let's go there together to celebrate...
- passing the test, Tae Hwan. - Okay. Let's do that.
I would've passed if I had someone like him.
Lee Jung, what kind of an excuse is that?
- Brother, let's watch it together. - Okay.
Hello.
Go over the rules with us.
(They get an instructional video before the driving test.)
It's my third time watching it.
- They look good together. - They're like father and son.
It's your first time, right?
- Yes. - It's my third time.
(Laughing)
(Nervous)
(Fine)
You'll be able to pass, so don't be nervous.
- You look nervous. - I was nervous.
You become more nervous with time. You need to take it right away.
- I know. That's the difference. - That's right. I agree.
Please pick up your belongings...
and head outside.
What is he going to do?
Take it with you.
- Tae Hwan, let's go together. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - This is making my heart beat fast.
You know that feeling, right?
I totally know that feeling. Seriously.
(It's time to reap the fruit of his hard work.)
(This is the battlefield.)
Look at the curved route.
You'll know if you've tried out...
for the Class Two Small Motorcycle License.
The track reminds me of tightroping...
because it's incredibly narrow.
It looks like it's this wide.
(Curved course)
- It's narrow. - It's narrow indeed.
(S-curve course)
Even when it's straight... Look at that.
I think that'll be easy.
That's the course I could mess up.
I think the same about that course.
- This course is fine. - That's right.
- It's easy. - Totally.
(Only one mistake is allowed.)
(I'm nervous.)
We'll begin the driving test for small motorcycles.
The first one is Park Tae Hwan.
(Tae Hwan goes first.)
- My goodness. - Sung Hwan's friend will go first.
Tae Hwan.
(Hugging)
- I'll do well. - He's confident.
- Oh, my. - We have elbow pads here.
- I'll do well. - Okay.
(Meanwhile, his legs go weak from being nervous.)
Put them on.
- I'll hold on to it. - Thank you.
(I feel nervous.)
This is driving me crazy.
It looks like Tae Hwan is certain that he'll pass.
Please get on the motorcycle.
Please get on.
(I'll show you, Sung Hwan.)
I don't know what to think about him. I'm a bit anxious.
I think he'll pass very easily.
- We can't say that for sure. - Really?
- To be honest, I'm not certain. - Really?
I think he'll pass since he can eat five packets of ramyeon.
He's experienced.
Tae Hwan, good luck.
Park Tae Hwan, raise your right hand if you're ready.
(Raising)
Let's go.
Park Tae Hwan, raise your right hand if you're ready.
(Raising)
Let's go.
(He steps on the gas without hesitation.)
(Lightning-fast start)
- He's driving so fast. - He's...
- I'm nervous. - I think he'll pass.
- He's driving so fast. - He's either the best driver...
or a complete newbie.
I've never heard that engine sound at a driving test center.
He stepped on the gas.
(Speeding up)
You have gone away from the course.
(Oh, no.)
What?
(Due to the speed, he goes off course.)
Why is he going so fast?
(Is he in a hurry?)
Did he think he needed to speed to get the points?
"Do I need to speed?"
He wanted to show Sung Hwan.
- "I can ride pretty well." - Yes.
- "I'll show you, Sung Hwan." - I bet he did that.
- "I'll show you." Vroom. - Vroom.
You have gone away from the course.
(He loses points as soon as he begins.)
(He needs to complete the course without making any mistakes.)
Points deducted for stepping on the ground.
You have failed to meet the minimum score.
Where are you going?
Hey.
(This is insane.)
- What is he going to do? - He showed us what not to do.
("The Art of Faults" by Park Tae Hwan)
(Shouting)
Points deducted for stepping on the ground.
You have failed to meet the minimum score.
(What's up with him?)
(A strong man who doesn't need to practice)
(I'll pass in 1 go.)
Get off.
- For real? - It's over.
"For real?"
(He suddenly asked if it was for real.)
You really become that way.
You become so confused once you fail.
- I mean... - He misspoke...
- since he was flustered. - It happens.
"For real?"
Get off.
- For real? - It's over.
(Tae Hwan suddenly becomes small.)
Please begin after listening to the verbal instructions.
Well done.
(Embarrassed)
Look at that facial expression.
Well done.
It's hard.
He's cute.
- It's okay. - It's hard.
- You get nervous when you go first. - It's so scary.
It's so scary.
He suddenly became weak.
Now, he looks like someone who was born in 2006.
I get it now.
- Tae Hwan, well done. - Thank you.
It's okay to fail on your first try.
I failed twice.
It isn't easy to pass...
without practice.
You just need to get through the first course. Watch carefully.
When you take the test again...
Once you pass the first course, you'll pass the test.
He passed.
(Finally, someone passes.)
- He's good. - His driving is steady.
You've passed.
(Cheering)
I'm so jealous.
- I was so jealous. - Anyone would be jealous.
If everyone else passes...
- No. - I feel bad for Tae Hwan.
You tested the waters this time, right?
You'll pass next time.
- You've failed. - Oh, no.
The motorcycle is heavy.
You've been disqualified.
Well done.
(Consoling)
You have gone away from the course.
You've failed.
There are a lot of people who fail the test right there.
You have gone away from the course.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
I've been on my motorcycle for a while...
and that was why I thought it would be easy.
(That's a shame.)
The curve. Let's just do well with the curve.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Tae Hwan stays with him without going home.)
- Ku Sung Hwan. - Right.
(Sung Hwan finally gets called.)
- Right. - These are for your elbows.
- Right. - These are for your knees.
- This was when I felt most nervous. - Thank you.
Gosh, this is so thrilling.
Don't get nervous.
I'll make it if I don't get nervous.
- Don't get nervous. - With the way things went,
around 60 percent of the group failed the test.
"Away from the course." I kept hearing that.
The trauma from my past two failures suddenly filled my mind.
That was why my heart beat even faster.
Give me a hug, Tae Hwan.
Tae Hwan is stuck there without being able to go home.
Good luck!
- Gosh, I feel so nervous! - You can do this!
I'll be waiting for you! Good luck!
- Ku Sung Hwan. - Yes.
(It's Ku Sung Hwan's turn.)
I really hope he makes it.
(It's time to show my skills.)
Good luck!
- Yes! - Yes!
I think he can make it.
With the feeling he got earlier.
- Right. - Remember that moment.
Gosh, I'm just practicing right now.
(Don't get nervous.)
The test will begin.
Please depart.
(Determined)
Please!
(Wait for me, my fantasy.)
(I hope you come back after passing the test.)
(This is a lucky place.)
(Good things will come.)
- I'm 100 percent certain I'll pass. - Everyone...
- wished for him to pass. - Nice. You're good.
(For those who are waiting for him)
He got a lot of great energy.
- The test will begin. - So many people rooted for him.
(He bravely takes off.)
Stay calm!
(Calm)
- Please. - He looks relaxed.
- He has to go like that. - He looks relaxed.
(He relaxedly enters the curve course.)
- Okay! - Gosh, that was very smooth.
Points deducted for stepping on the ground.
(Screaming)
(A terrible sight)
- Are you serious? - It felt too slow!
Isn't it over then?
- I don't remember a thing. - Why not just move with both feet?
- Like this. - Gosh.
- It's like Ronaldo doing stepovers. - Gosh.
(Dumbfounded)
That was the double step.
(Stepping)
Points deducted for stepping on the ground.
You have gone away from the course.
You have failed to meet the minimum score.
"You have failed to meet the minimum score."
(Losing 20 points)
(Losing 10 points)
Just move with both feet.
- He lost 40 points in 5 seconds. - He lost 40 points in 5 seconds.
Come down carefully.
- Come down carefully. - He's unqualified.
Can I not try just one more time?
(Can I not try just one more time?)
(He ends up pathetically asking for another chance.)
I look so pathetic!
- You end up thinking that way. - Right.
- It ended so quickly. - He was that desperate.
- Right. - Right.
Is this place cursed for driving licenses?
Why is everyone failing?
I didn't fail that quickly though.
- That was just... - But...
Tae Hwan went past that course.
You're worse than Tae Hwan.
The lines looked blurry when I practiced.
I took off with that image in my head.
The lines can be seen totally fine.
The lines could be seen too well.
That threw me off.
- What are you saying? - You're saying that's an issue?
(His excuses are shocking.)
I can totally relate to that.
The grass felt much greener than I thought.
- Right! - The sky was way too blue.
- Right! - What are you saying?
- I'm serious! - Why does the sky being blue...
- even matter? - What does that mean?
When I practiced,
- I couldn't see the lines. - I know what he's talking about.
- They were way too visible. - They were way too yellow, right?
- Totally. - How would they be too yellow?
Why does the grass even matter?
You seem to get very nervous, Jung.
- Right. - Sung Hwan.
You'll be fine if you overcome that.
Get your license first before you speak.
(Right!)
Points deducted for stepping on the ground.
He's running over.
You have failed to meet the minimum score.
Come down carefully.
- Can I not try just one more time? - No.
That finger is hilarious.
Please head back.
I think he failed the fastest today out of the test takers.
(Driving off)
(Left alone)
- He just drives off like that? - Right.
- That's... - I got a ride back.
He can just walk back as he didn't move that much.
He barely went anywhere.
(Holding his laughter)
Touching the nose means it's really funny.
You did your best.
I felt so embarrassed to see Tae Hwan's face.
That's how it feels.
How many times have I failed now?
We've both died in battle.
(We've both died in battle.)
It's okay. We'll still get more opportunities.
- Right. - You've tried your best.
- I'll see you again. - Right.
I won't see you off. You can leave first.
I'll get back to you soon.
You should take the test with him again.
- Right. - Right.
Tae Hwan failed before my turn.
Because of him,
- Why is it his fault now? - I felt a lot more nervous.
He's making all sorts of excuses.
(He ends up blaming a guy 26 years younger.)
Tae Hwan rushed himself all because of you.
They say when a big accident happens,
the memory of that moment completely gets wiped out.
That happened to me.
I can't even remember where things went wrong.
The trust I had in my friend broke down...
and it brought me down as well.
What have I done?
(His way back home feels rather pathetic.)
That's an awful feeling.
(Failing the Test 3 Times Straight, It Actually Happened)
I wish to see the two of you riding together...
after passing the test.
Actually,
I took the test again today.
Did you pass?
- I made it. - Awesome!
He did it!
- I passed. - Awesome!
I have it all.
The Heavy Vehicle License.
The Class One Ordinary License and the Small Vehicle License.
- You look different now. - I can drive anything with wheels.
If we happen to go on a trip together,
I can drive a big bus for all of us.
- Hyun Moo should do the driving. - I can take care of it.
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
Congratulations!
(I Live Alone)
(The grand project of 2026)
(Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
(Working hard)
(The Grand Rainbow Bazaar is ready to begin.)
(Word wizard, Moomoo)
(Clothes professional, Storekeeper KUNST)
(Should we ask AI?)
(The one who handles prices, AI84)
(Participating wholeheartedly)
(It looks nice.)
(The one in charge of positive energy, Joy)
(All profits will be donated!)
(Let's take a look.)
(I want to buy the things there as well.)
(It attracted a lot of interest.)
(There are so many things I would like to buy.)
(Can I be there too?)
(Both hands full)
(A big spender appears.)
(Many people lined up to participate in the donation.)
(I'm not sure, to be honest.)
(Hands in pockets)
(A picky customer appears.)
(Struggling)
(Then, how about this, Tae Hyun? How old is your daughter?)
(Special measures taken for the picky customer)
(The keyring seems nice.)
(He video chats with his daughter right away.)
(It's so cute!)
(Should I buy this?)
(I'll take everything from here to there.)
(The Grand Rainbow Bazaar satisfies even the loving father.)
- What items are you selling? - Me?
Does your daughter like drawing?
What do you have?
The tablet PC for drawing.
Hey, Soo Jin. Take a look at this.
- Okay. - Do you know what this is?
It's something you can draw with.
It's hard to find someone who would do that much...
- for their daughter. - He's a great father.
I used this when I created my webtoons.
He used this when he created his webtoons.
I put it up for sale since I didn't use it.
- Right. - It would be great to have that.
Is that so?
This one is nice. My wife might scold me for this.
I didn't think that would get sold but it did.
- It should be cleaned once. - Right?
(Cleaning service for the new owner)
This has the perfect vibes of an eighth-grader.
It doesn't look too fancy...
and it can be used regularly.
She would definitely...
Joy offered to become a model.
That would make him buy it.
She said the bag looked nice.
- The bag. - Really?
I brought another thing with the vibes of an eighth-grader.
I'm not getting ahead of myself. This one looks even better.
You know how to sell things, Joy.
(This is cute as well, isn't it?)
It would look even cuter with the keyring.
This is the perfect place for keyrings.
Hold on. She likes that one as well.
- Right? - Okay.
He's smiling brightly.
It would look hilarious...
- with the youngest. - Sleepwear.
I have a feeling we'll get along well.
We wouldn't have sold anything to Tae Hyun without Joy.
You're right. We wouldn't have sold anything.
Have you sold things before?
- You're great at this. - It's my first time doing this.
You make things sound so pleasant.
Joy surprised me a lot.
She's the Sales Queen.
She recommended things without giving any time to breathe.
How much is everything?
- It's 1,030 dollars in total. - It's 1,030 dollars?
- Yes. - You're buying a lot of things.
It sounded like he wasn't going to buy anything, but I was wrong.
He's buying a lot of items.
He's getting 6 keyrings, 2 bags,
a jacket, a monitor,
two bottles of perfume, a pair of sunglasses,
- and a hat. - He bought a lot of things.
You're right.
- Let's stop at 1,030 dollars. - They're right there.
Who has come this time?
Who is it?
- Kang Yong! - Hello.
It's Kang Yong.
The announcers are here.
- I brought my seniors. - Oh, hello!
- Please come in. - The announcers.
They're the announcers of MBC.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Crowded)
(Kim Min Ho, Kim Joon Sang, Park So Young, )
(Jeong Young Han, Kang Da Eun)
(MBC announcers, great friends to meet)
- You have to hurry. - There are many women's items.
After Joy came,
- there are so many women's clothes. - I brought so many things.
There are so many things you can get.
(Hurrying)
I have to display the women's clothes.
This is the time.
(They become busy after letting in a large group of customers.)
- He's struggling a lot. - Gosh.
He quietly helped me a lot with everything.
We have to sell a lot of women's clothes here.
Right.
We won't have that many female customers.
Which one? It's down there.
Hello.
Gosh, it's a large group.
- Hello. - Hello.
There are many things to buy here.
Hello. There are women's clothes here.
- I have to get my mom something. - Your mom?
How is this coat for your mother?
- It looks great. - It looks nice, doesn't it?
- How is it? - How much is it?
This? This is 60 dollars.
- It's 60 dollars? - Yes.
Great.
I should've bought it if it was sold for 60 dollars.
(That's so cheap.)
- It's 60 dollars? - Yes.
- Who is this for? - My mom.
Kang Yong?
Gosh, this is so pretty!
- It looks great on you! - I wanted a furry jacket like this.
Gosh!
You can definitely try it on.
It's Joy's item.
- Remember that. - It's such an honor!
(Interested)
This is yours.
You look just like a Red Velvet member.
Look at you and your lines.
(The customer's heart shakes with the ultimate line.)
- That's not it! - Will you buy this?
How much is this?
It's 50 dollars.
- I'll buy it! - It must be a lot more expensive.
- Right? - It's for my mom.
It looks great on you!
Gosh! Don't tell me you're not going to buy this one.
This one is cute.
It's perfect.
How do I look?
You can't resist that.
(You can't resist that.)
Gosh.
- Can I sweep things away? - Of course.
I've already chosen several items.
- I'll send 1,100 dollars. - Really?
Thank you.
- I've sent the money, Hyun Moo. - Right.
I'll get going now.
- I hope you make a lot. - Get back safely.
- It'll be used for a great cause. - Okay. Bye.
He sent 1,100 dollars.
- He sent 1,100 dollars? - Yes.
- How about that? - These are worth 300 dollars.
- What about Young Han? - These look nice.
- This is for women. - They were used twice.
Isn't this for babies?
Try striking a nice pose.
Things went wild while you went down to say goodbye.
Not a lot of talking is needed as it's a large group.
- They can talk amongst themselves. - Right.
And...
since there are many customers, it becomes a competition.
- Right. - Right.
They were originally 300 dollars. I'll sell them for 100 dollars.
- What? - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
They're my friends.
- Hello. - Ha Young and Yerin.
- Hello. - They must be best friends.
A lot of women's clothes got sold already.
Really?
Apink!
Gosh, it's Yerin.
Take a look.
I felt a lot more comfortable with my friends.
It's great to see them during these moments.
How much is this?
Right. Just a moment.
It feels like an underground mall.
It feels like...
the four of us opened up a store.
- That was the only thing available. - You should get it.
- Totally. - It's really hard to get.
Don't hesitate to ask about the price.
- Right. - Kang Yong!
- What are you going to do? - Gosh, I feel exhausted.
I think my mom will wear it every single day.
- I'm serious. - This is nice.
Your mom will love this.
It must've been exhausting.
- Right. - Right.
(Exhausted)
(In pain)
- This one. - It looks nice.
What is he doing?
(I can't carry on.)
- What is he doing? - What?
(He's completely knocked down.)
Not being able to breathe properly is a big issue.
It'll be tough with so many people around.
I think...
it was my cold with a runny nose.
I started to feel drowsy.
I felt like an actual clothes store employee.
I let people ask me questions...
and I just stood there spacing out.
Gosh, being the treasurer?
It completely changed my mindset.
I felt so much respect toward my soccer team's treasurer.
I can't keep the customers waiting for too long.
I can't get the numbers wrong.
- But the numbers keep changing. - Right.
More and more people kept coming in.
It was really tough.
Storekeepers are amazing.
I had to say the same things over and over again.
It was really tough.
The three of us have similar vibes.
They started early in the morning.
- Of course, it's exhausting. - Right.
It feels like Dongmyo here.
That's 100 dollars, Joy.
He came up with the prices in the midst of all that.
(Sighing)
(He hurries down to welcome the next customer while groaning.)
Gosh, I'm dying.
- Hey! - Gosh.
You all aren't ready to welcome a guest.
- Come in. - Right.
He sounds boring starting with his first line.
(Say it with me, everyone!)
(Holy!)
Gosh.
(The one that shares a holy friendship with Hyun Moo)
(Announcer Han Suk Joon)
The first floor is the electronics store.
Okay. The first floor?
It's the electronics store.
- The electronics store? - Are you not into baking?
Baking? Oh, thank you.
Gosh, that oven. I'm sick of even looking at it now.
Gosh.
My daughter loves it when I bake things for her.
- This is used in bakeries. - This one?
How many times did you introduce that?
Gosh, I'm sick of it.
We have an oven at home.
You have to replace it with a top-tier one.
You have to make good things for Sa Bin.
How much did you pay for that oven?
- That oven was around... - It's an expensive one.
It was expensive. It was around...
- Wasn't it expensive? - Did you pay a lot for it?
Before you talk about the price,
- you should talk about the oven. - For Jae Hyeon.
The oven from the same brand...
that is below the level of that one is used in bakeries.
- Right. - That one is at the very top.
And there's something that holds it up.
That was custom-made with my own money.
- You're giving away both of them? - Right.
The original price was around 3,500 dollars to 4,000 dollars.
I'll give everything away for 1,000 dollars.
- That's a steal. - That's a great deal.
- Everything together. - Okay. I'll get it for 1,000.
- Okay! - Okay!
That's the third item sold!
- Are you really going to buy it? - I'll get it for 1,000 dollars.
Is this for sale?
(He tried smell marketing after baking early in the morning.)
(But the oven was rejected each time.)
(The new owner of our oven was this close to us.)
I have a friend who wants to open a cafe.
I can give it to my friend as a gift.
- That's a great idea. - I'll keep it with me for now.
- That's a great idea. - That's great.
It'll be used for a good cause as well.
- Right. - Right.
(Be happy, oven!)
- No? - That's a no for me.
Okay.
I bought a lot of things.
- Gosh, look at Kang Yong. - I bought so many things.
Look at Kang Yong's smile.
Come down to the first floor if you are ready to pay.
- Okay. - Bring everything down.
We'll check things out downstairs.
- Hold on. - It should be done again.
- Let's get it sorted again. - For now,
I have everything written down for the Announcer Team.
- It should be for each person. - Write down their names.
- How much is this? - It's 30 dollars.
The sneakers are 100 dollars.
We didn't decide on anything,
but we automatically found our own roles.
- The glasses. - The glasses?
- And lastly, the padded jacket. - How much is this one?
This one.
- It's 100 dollars. - It's 100 dollars.
- We're done, right? - Thank you!
- Thank you! - Thank you!
They spent a lot with a good heart.
Thank you!
This is awesome.
They're Sa Bin's competitors.
(They're Sa Bin's competitors.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Yerin and Ha Young. - They were still there.
Competitors?
- Hello. - Hello.
- How old is Sa Bin? - She's a first-grader.
- She's a first-grader? - She's quite big now.
She'll go wild with the Labubu.
- The Labubu is right here. - Keyrings.
They're selling things to him.
Isn't this backpack so cute?
She will definitely love that one.
Without a doubt. This is perfect for Sa Bin.
- Girls would love these. - Gosh!
They would go crazy.
- They love these. - "They would go crazy."
- What's with your lines? - "They would go crazy."
- They won't go crazy. - She currently wears...
pajamas with this character.
You must buy that then.
You're quite good at this.
- She's definitely Joy's friend. - Right.
- Take a good look. - Right.
There are a lot of great items.
- Won't she like this? - I should get this.
- Right. - This is it.
- Joy had it with her. - So that was how that got sold.
It's a mystery box. You'll get one of these.
If my dad buys me that,
- he would be the best dad ever. - Right.
That would be the best gift.
- What about this? - The pink one.
Hold on. I had my eyes on that. This is also a hat.
It's Joy's. It's brand new.
(It's Joy's.)
How cute would she look with this?
- This would be nice. - She must like pink.
It looks really nice.
- Great! - Great!
It feels great to get things for my child.
I've seen Sa Bin before.
I'm recommending things that would suit her.
Exactly. Thank you.
What about your wife?
I got something for my wife.
What was it again? The cleansing wipes.
Gosh!
- I got these for my wife. - Suk Joon!
You're just getting cleansing wipes for your wife?
She looks beautiful after washing her face.
I get that, but...
- Don't try to end it with those. - No.
- Here you are. - Thank you.
Get them checked out on the first floor.
- He got everything that's pink. - Right.
- He got all of the pink items. - He's a great father.
(Another customer arrives at that moment.)
It's not just for you.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hey!
It's Yong Wook.
- From "Culinary Class Wars." - Right.
(Director of Barbecue Research in "Culinary Class Wars")
You look different in person.
- This is Chef Yoo Yong Wook. - Hello.
What are the sections?
These are women's clothes,
- Oh, women's clothes. - and those are men's.
- Men's clothes. - More women's clothes in the room.
Okay.
What is this? Goodness.
- It's what I brought. - Which one?
I've never used it.
- So you'd need to clean it. - It's all right.
- It's... - It's no problem.
- Oh, it's a drip coffee maker? - It's for camping.
- All right. - He likes camping and coffee.
- You know this famous brand, right? - Good. All right.
- Chef, you like camping? - I love camping.
- What is it? - I have an amazing item.
A pop-up tent.
It's a pop-up tent.
You said we shouldn't pop it open.
- Because it's hard to fold back. - You'll have to buy it...
once we open it.
It's cheap.
- This... - It's 100 dollars.
Can I check its brand?
- Its brand? It has no brand. - Yes.
Once you throw it...
- Like that. - A pop-up.
- Goodness. - It's convenient.
It's so convenient.
But you don't have to buy it unwillingly.
- That's right. - You opened it?
- Hey, how do we fold this? - I'll do it.
Do you know how to fold it?
- He doesn't know how to fold it. - How do we fold it?
A camper would know.
- You have to... - Don't you have to twist this?
- No? - You must be right.
- You're smart. - Hold on.
A camper is indeed different.
- He folded it at once. - Like this?
No, wait.
I guess you can't do it alone.
Wait. I think he's not going to get it because of this.
But this is what makes it fun. It's memorable.
- He calls struggles a memory. - It becomes an episode.
I don't think this is it.
I'm sorry, but you have to buy it because you opened it.
How do I carry it home? I don't think I can go through the door.
It's raining, so use it as an umbrella.
(It's raining, so use it as an umbrella.)
Let me try folding it back.
You should go shopping.
- I'll go see the clothes. - Yes.
- This will fit me, right? - I only wore it once.
- You want me to wear this? - Yes.
I got it from Hong Kong Disneyland.
Here.
This and this.
(Rustling)
Look at Kian84 folding it.
It's a Type-C charger,
- so it's easy to charge. - Yes, I can go and charge it.
(Feeling bad)
(Kian84's tent is harder to fold than expected.)
Darn.
(That's how his lonely fight began.)
Kian84, I'll throw it on my way out.
What? Why would you throw it? It's new.
(Hoping there'd be an answer somewhere)
Oh, no.
- A color combination you like. - Great.
I got it.
Oh, gosh. He folded it.
(Laughing)
It's easy.
(This is the moment)
Oh, gosh. He folded it.
(They realized something.)
Don't lose it.
Hey, this is really convenient.
(If you don't give up until the end, )
(you'll achieve it!)
(That's right!)
(Overwhelmed)
- Ring me up, please. - Okay.
- It's 600 dollars. - It's 600 dollars.
Then I'll donate the change.
- It's 650 dollars then. - All right?
Here you go.
- Please put it to good use. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- Thank you for these. Bye. - Bye.
- Thank you. See you around. - Bye.
- Bye. - See you around, Hyun Moo.
Shall we rest for ten minutes?
- This... - Goodness.
That's when Hyun Moo started napping.
(The owners are out of energy.)
We got to cheer up more...
- because you came. - Really?
Hey, someone is here.
All right. Who is it?
- Who is it? - Hello?
- Gosh, Sung Tae! - Goodness.
It's Heo Sung Tae.
(Don't talk about villains without me.)
(Unmatched, commanding charisma)
(Actor Heo Sung Tae)
What are you here to get?
- What do you need? - No idea. I'll check out first.
But there must be something you need to buy.
(Reading the room with his hands put together politely)
"I can use this money for good causes and get this as well."
- I don't need anything much. - Is that so?
Then I'll recommend some.
Great. Joy made a good move.
We have workout equipment here.
That's it.
She's good.
They have great teamwork.
All we have left is that...
- and an oven. - An oven for baking.
(It's me, an oven for baking.)
Aren't you into baking?
Not at all.
(Giving him carp bread for now)
We never run out of carp bread.
You can use it for other purposes if you want, right?
It does everything.
You can leave it on...
- when it's cold. - Of course.
(Selling it wholeheartedly)
Do you like luxury goods?
- No, not at all. - No?
- Is that so? - I think it'll look good on you.
- Would you like to try it on? - Try it on.
- It's not that cheap, but... - I don't think it'll fit.
(He tries it on when he's told so.)
(Amazed)
You look about ten years younger.
(His hands are put together shyly.)
I look like a thug a little.
- It's pretty, right? - It's pretty.
(Shy)
This color suits you.
Is this men's?
These days, clothes are gender-neutral.
It's for men.
She must've been unsure.
- I didn't know whose it was. - Right?
Will Mom wear this?
It's totally made for a mom.
- I'm sure your mom will like it. - Of course. It's colorful.
(Is that so?)
I bought it for over 3,000 dollars. It's mine.
I think 1,000 dollars will be enough for it.
- What, 1,000 dollars? Suddenly? - Yes. Since this is 50 dollars,
you can pay 950 dollars for it.
Since this is for a good cause,
I can't discount a whole lot.
If you get this for 1,000 dollars, this will be on the house.
- So, for 1,000 dollars, - Yes.
I'm getting this and... Will you give me that?
- We will. - Then I'll get them for 1,000.
(Then I'll get them for 1,000 dollars.)
- You're a great son. - I think your mom will like it.
Your mom will like it.
He bought it for his mom.
- Let's go upstairs and... - Yes. There's a lot more upstairs.
- Upstairs is the real deal. - There's a lot upstairs.
- These are Joy's clothes. - You're right.
I used up 1,000 dollars...
because I thought you only had stuff downstairs.
- You can check them out. - Take a look around freely.
(Hesitant)
Whose shoe lift insole is this?
- Which one? - Isn't this a shoe lift insole?
- Oh, it's not. - It's not.
Do you run?
Why does everyone smell them?
(Sniffing)
- They smelled them even with a tag. - It's a new pair.
When you're offered a new role...
(Speaking of these loafers...)
(In the morning, to find the owner of the loafers, )
(Hyun Moo seduced everyone.)
(But it won't fit.)
(But everyone rejected them and criticized him.)
(In the end, the red loafers couldn't find their owner.)
(The loafers have no fault.)
(We're the problem.)
(Will he be convinced this time?)
You must wear these if you shoot "The Roundup" again.
(The loafers are a bit too much for even Sung Tae, who is shy.)
(Putting them on)
- They look good on him. - They look really good on him.
- They're really nice. - Do you want to look in the mirror?
Hey, go over there.
That was smooth.
Hey, you might land a new role.
(Leading him to the restroom naturally)
You might land a new role.
What's wrong with him?
"Moving excitedly?"
They look good on him.
- They look good on him. - The glasses...
You might land a new role.
How much are these?
- They're from Gentle Monster. - The original price...
- must be around 300 dollars. - What?
- But... - They're from Gentle Monster.
But I'll give them to you at 50 dollars.
Is that so?
It seems like he rarely buys things.
I know him a bit, and he doesn't buy clothes at all.
He seems like he wouldn't.
If you want to land a role on OTT...
- For OTT... - Try them on.
- Not OTT, - Or these.
But a new role in Sci-Fi projects.
I was looking for someone who'd suit these.
I think they'll look great on you.
- That's right. - I don't know any fashion brands.
So I'm telling you.
- These... Gosh! - They're the real deal.
- I mean it! - No, I don't buy it.
- No, with a shearling jacket... - That was least convincing.
- It'll look good with your jacket. - No. How about...
trying these on top of them?
(Rushed)
Gosh, how am I supposed to sell these?
I felt rushed toward the end.
- Sung Tae. It's my first time... - People don't suit these well.
Seeing anyone suit them.
I don't suit fancy things.
- Not at all! - What are you talking about?
Those sunglasses only suit him.
They look good on him even now.
Which one do you like better?
No, I'll just...
The one I liked was... Which one was it?
- Which one? - The one he said...
he'd sell at 50 dollars.
You're getting Gentle Monster glasses at 50 dollars.
You're basically earning money.
- Sung Tae. - They look good on you too.
- They look good on you. - These too.
Give him this.
(Toe corrector)
- A toe corrector? - Your toes are all twisted, right?
I'll take this.
(Offensive)
- How did you know? - Aren't all your toes like this?
At our age, our toes are all twisted.
- Oh, your toes? - They're not aligned. Yes.
This is Level One,
- so you start with this. - That's right.
Joy became absorbed from this moment on.
These look good on you. Try them on again.
- These are... - Oh, my.
I think they look good on you.
- They're so pretty. - It's a bit...
(The queen of sales brings something over.)
- This is not bad. - The price...
- You brought over a wig? - No way.
- Do you want this as a free gift? - This...
is a free gift.
- No, it's okay. - Come on!
(Flustered)
- I happened to... - You must get this.
- We're sure about this. - You look like a college kid.
(Right when they were making sales with random remarks)
- Someone is here. - Someone is here.
(Who is it?)
- Hello. - Oh, you're here.
- The rappers. - They're here.
How have you been?
(A distinctively attractive mid-low voice)
(Rapper Woo Won Jae)
(A stylish and soulful rapper)
(Rapper Coogie)
- It's Coogie and Won Jae. - Won Jae.
- Hello. - Hey!
- Come on in. - Hello.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- The rappers. - Hello.
- Woo Won Jae. - I'm really sorry,
but you guys came a little late.
You should just get these.
It's not bad.
Until when will you maintain the same image?
- I should seek change with this? - Yes.
Check them. These are yours.
- Wait. - Wait.
Why do people keep sniffing them?
(Sniffing)
They all do that as soon as they take them.
They smell them.
- It smells like radish pickle. - Radish pickle?
- It looks good on Won Jae. - It's perfect for him.
They're basically yours.
They suit you.
- They look good on him, right? - They look good.
- Good for him. - Do they look okay?
They look really good on Won Jae.
- This is crazy. - I'm just trying them on.
I didn't know there were people who suit these.
The color suits him.
Carry this with those on, Won Jae.
(Selling another item while he's at it)
(Glancing)
Are your toes okay?
(Like this)
(Proud)
He's feeling proud.
We're donating the money.
You donate often anyway.
You donated your money,
and you got an ukulele for free.
When you just donated.
I see. Then...
You keep captivating me.
- Then, do you... - Are you getting them all?
- Yes. - Feel free to look around.
- I just tried them on. - He's holding this.
(Hesitant)
Sung Tae, check that section out.
There are a few good things over there.
- Excuse me. - All right.
- Sung Tae will check that out. - Come this way.
Take a look around freely.
We have men's clothes here.
These are for women.
This is new.
They're mostly new.
- These two? - Yes.
This is 100 dollars.
This should be around 50 dollars.
Then it's 100 and 50 dollars.
(Total: 150 dollars)
- Then... - Yes?
On top of 1,150 dollars,
can I not take the stepper from downstairs?
- I don't think I'll use it. - Right.
Sure.
He must've really not wanted to take it.
But this alone is 400 dollars.
- I mean... - Then I'll pay 1,200 dollars.
- At 1,200, take the glasses too. - At 1,200 dollars...
Then in total, I'll pay 1,200 dollars.
- All right. - And...
- I'll leave the stepper. - All right.
That's 500 dollars.
- Yes. - Then I'll bring it.
- Oh, here it is. - Yes, write it down.
Didn't he want to pay 1,200 for everything?
- That's right. - Correct.
Give it to Sung Tae for 1,200 dollars.
(Sung Tae's list of purchases: Jacket for Mother, two clothings...)
(Putting them in properly)
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Thank you for calling me for a good cause.
Sure. Actor Heo Sung Tae is leaving.
- I'll go now, - Actor Heo Sung Tae is leaving.
- so they can focus. - Sung Tae.
- Use the restroom. There's none. - Take this too.
- Thank you. How should I use it? - It's a free gift.
- We just gave out everything. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
- Let me use the restroom. - Yes, use it before you go.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
- Yes. - It looks like he got drained.
Are you selling this comic book?
What is that?
- That? It's Kian84's. - But...
- For sure. - But that collection...
is missing Volume Eight. You have to imagine it.
Imagine it?
- Does that even make sense? - He's just saying whatever.
I had to sell it anyhow. It was coming to an end.
- This is the series. - There's more on the inside.
- Yes. - Is that so?
- Items for your mom or sister. - Really?
- Can he take this? - Behind them...
- He bowed when no one was looking. - No one was looking.
- I really didn't see him. - I didn't either.
He left in case...
- we came out to send him off. - He left quietly.
- Then... - Who is it?
- As long as it's not small. - I'll get it.
- This... - It's never been worn.
(Yanking)
- Hello. - Yes, hello.
- Our last customer. - Gosh, Sean.
(A prominent runner in the entertainment industry)
(Famous philanthropist, Sean)
He's amazing.
Gosh, he's truly amazing.
(Philanthropist Sean came at once at the news...)
(of a bazaar for donation.)
Runner Sean is here.
Please write something for our guestbook.
We don't have a lot left.
(Scribbling)
I knew it.
Goodness.
- "Sharing is life." - "Sharing is life."
That's Sean's kind of life.
That kept lingering on my mind even after going home.
- "Sharing is life?" - Yes.
It feels more real as it comes from someone who's practicing it.
It's almost empty because people bought a lot.
Right.
All his stuff is in good condition.
- The king of splurging is here. - Gosh, Sean.
The king of splurging?
Seriously, the things he says...
- The king of splurging? - It's sophisticated, right?
- Are you still running? - I'm running from time to time.
It's been so long.
- I know. - Right.
(Wait, this voice...)
(Reacting automatically)
You should go and greet him.
- Go greet him. - You must.
The respected hip-hop senior has arrived, so...
It was probably their first time seeing him.
(The class of Korea's hip-hop)
(The hip-hop warrior with 29 years of career)
(Sean of JINUSEAN)
- Goodness. - Why is he so intimidated?
(The veteran rapper and newcomers)
I've never seen rappers behaving that way.
(A nerve-racking first encounter)
(Approaching their senior hesitantly)
He wanted to say hi.
- Oh, hi. Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- It's Coogie and Won Jae. - Right.
I've been seeing your work.
It must've not been easy.
(Joking)
You've never seen us so polite, right?
Let's get back to work.
I've never seen them like that.
It's been a while since I saw them putting their hands together.
There are clothes for kids.
There are many fun things here. We have running shoes too.
Do you ever shop, though?
- I rarely do. - Rarely, right?
How old is your daughter?
(Based on what they learned from their previous sales, )
(they go after his children!)
- My 1st child is 19. - She's 19.
And the youngest is 14.
- She's 14? - Yes.
All right. Then I'll leave it to Joy.
This is Calvin Klein.
(The queen of sales starts selling right away.)
This is pretty.
- Right? - Yes.
- I think it'll fit. - My first child is really skinny.
- It's medium. - Medium?
Then it'll be too big for her.
- It's a smaller version. - She's really skinny.
- It could be an overfit. - This fits me too.
- Oh, in that case... - Okay. We'll include this.
- All right. - Put that in.
(Making his first purchase after listening to Joy)
- There are so many good things. - What is this?
Wouldn't your mother like this? Is it too big?
My mom's feet are a bit weak.
- So, this could be... - He thinks of his mom a lot.
Won Jae is a good son.
It's better to give her something...
- that she might not have. - That's a good idea.
Either this...
I think the size will be perfect.
Won Jae, should I start settling the bill?
- That was a good purchase. - Yes, CODE KUNST.
Please settle the bill for everything.
- Are you wearing them out? - Yes, I'll keep them on.
- Then let's... - He's getting the shoes? Gucci?
- He didn't take them off. - He even wore them out.
- He did? - He didn't take them off.
- They look good on him. - They do.
That means I have a good eye.
- You're right. - It's just that they don't suit me.
It's 923 dollars in total.
Then 1,000 dollars?
No, just wire 950 dollars.
- CODE KUNST, I make money too. - Yes?
- All right. - "I make money too."
Won Jae will pay 1,000 when his total is 900 dollars.
- Thank you, Won Jae. - I'll make it 1,000 dollars.
- You'll be blessed. - It's 1,000 dollars...
for both Coogie and Won Jae.
- Okay. - Both of them are spending 1,000.
- Yes. - Yet, they're so young.
(Coogie's list of purchases: Kian84's comic book...)
You'll be blessed.
I brought 700 dollars,
I'll wire...
- You'll wire it? - the remaining 300 dollars.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Hello?
Mom, can you wire me 300 dollars more?
- I... - "Wire me 300 more, Mom."
- It's for a good cause. - He's so cute.
- He's really cute. - Won Jae...
gives all his earnings...
- to his parents. - He gives them all?
And he gets an allowance from them.
- He's really nice. - What a good son.
He's amazing.
- Mom wired it. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, Won Jae.
- Bye. Good to see you. - Bye.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Since he's our last customer,
take a look around freely from here.
What are some of the things he could get?
Give me all of them.
- Sean, for real? - No.
(Are these better?)
I brought this to show you.
- What is it? - What is it?
The finisher medal for all seven major marathons.
- Oh, the one I asked about? - The one you asked.
Is this the one?
(Tokyo, Boston, London, Berlin, Chicago, and New York marathon)
It's not easy to complete all seven major marathons.
And he did it all within one year.
That's right.
Gosh, he's truly amazing.
I think he came to show us that.
(Joking)
He suddenly took that out.
(He's as eager to brag about it as he's eager to donate.)
During the seventh marathon, you get one more number.
On the back, there's a sign that says...
you've run 6 marathons and that this is the 7th.
So you wear that number on the back and front.
So when you run, everyone cheers for you.
- Could you shop now? - Right, I should.
- We can't just stand and talk. - Right.
(Right, I should shop.)
(He calls someone right away.)
- Hello. - Hey, Tae Eun.
- Hi, have you been well? - Yes, I have.
There's a bunch of clothes here.
He's not his biological son.
It's someone he's been sponsoring since young.
- Oh, someone he sponsors? - Yes, a teenager he sponsors.
He videocalled him so he could buy clothes for him.
- What? - Do you like it?
Do you like this?
You do? Okay.
Then I'll get six of these, okay?
- He bought a lot. - Yes.
It's like he took the whole rack.
When they're in good condition, it's around 300 to 350 dollars.
- Then let's make it 350. - All right, 350 it is.
- These are yours. - All right.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
- He didn't get any for himself. - Right.
He didn't get anything for him.
- He bought them to share. - They were all for others.
- It's 1,770 dollars. - It's 1,770 dollars?
- Then... - Yes.
(Tapping)
Gosh, Sean!
- What is it? - Well...
- Gosh. - What is it?
Gosh, why did you wire so much?
Since it's for a good cause.
(Total: 1,770 dollars)
He paid twice as much. Sean.
(Total amount he wired: 3,000 dollars)
He came and splurged on them.
He literally lives a life of sharing.
(He practices a life of sharing.)
- Take care, Sean. Thank you. - Bye.
Great work, everyone.
Sean, seriously...
- Thank you so much! - Sean!
- Thank you so much. - You'll have a long way home.
You need to press that.
- Thank you, Sean... - Do you need an oven?
The oven?
I asked just in case.
- Thank you. - Sure. Bye.
- Thank you. - Bye.
- Take care. - Goodness. We did a great job.
It ended.
(After the last customer left...)
Well...
- Let's rest for five minutes. - Yes, rest up.
I mean...
I was so tired.
(Plopping down)
- Seriously... - Like bobsleigh!
Gosh, I'm dying.
(Rushing to rest, faster than anyone)
- Great work, everyone. - Good job, everyone.
- Gosh. - A flea market isn't for everyone.
(Goodness)
(Smiling)
(Getting the red jumpsuit)
I thought you'd be cold.
He looked cold.
(Covering up Fathermoo lying on the floor)
- Gosh, Joy. - She's warm-hearted.
- She's sweet. - Thank you.
- You're warm-hearted. - Hyun Moo, that fits you perfectly.
I think you should get it. The height is perfect.
You look like Po of Teletubbies.
- You're right. He looks like Po. - It's cute.
(Cute)
This is the color of the shoes that Won Jae got.
We should've sold it to Won Jae to match his shoes.
Seriously.
(Gosh, we got through it.)
(Taking a break about 12 hours after waking up)
We were a perfect team.
He turned on the AI on his own.
And I didn't even tell him to.
CODE KUNST was settling the bill on his own.
She didn't run out of energy.
And I asked questions to the customers.
- Our teamwork was perfect. - That's amazing.
(They did a great job today.)
It must be as tiring as moving.
Yes.
(Only the queen of sales is full of energy.)
- Someone is here? - Gosh, what is this?
- What? - What?
(What?)
We thought Sean was the last customer.
- That's right. - Yes.
Sir.
Mr. Jun?
- Mr. Jun, I'm here. - He came again.
It's Dex?
(Who is it?)
Why are you back?
- "Why are you back?" - Why is he here?
- Mr. Jun. - Are we back to square one?
(Are we back to square one?)
"Square one?"
Didn't you think, "Are we starting again?"
"Are we back to the morning?"
I didn't take the TV earlier.
Don't you need an oven?
Wait. An oven?
Hyun Moo, I can't take that.
We'll deliver it for you.
You're trying to sell until the end.
Of course.
He's full of energy.
Don't mind me. I'll check them out on my own.
(Approaching)
(Adding another item on Fathermoo)
- What is that? - I thought it'd be too bright.
It makes me feel solemn.
DF.
(Decorating Fathermoo)
Are you taking them all?
(Dex shops like crazy while Fathermoo is asleep.)
- It's so nice. - Right.
(Snoring)
Oh, my. I snored?
You slept. You got a good sleep.
Oh, my.
(Snoring loudly)
I had no idea.
- You snored a lot, Hyun Moo. - I must've passed out.
(Fathermoo is soundly asleep.)
Hyun Moo!
He's sleeping for real.
(Patting)
(What is this?)
(Scratching)
- He's still here? - Yes.
It hasn't been long.
- You came a while ago. - It hasn't been long.
- Add it to that. - He bought more?
- I included it. - Okay.
(Rummaging through)
- It's perfect on you. - Hold on.
- You became a British man. - You look great.
- Look at this. - They're all in it together.
- Is this yours? - They're all in it together.
That's what I wore here.
Is that so? It's yours?
I wore that here.
He's buying whatever he sees.
But that coat was pretty.
It's 785 dollars.
Yes. Thank you.
If it's 785 dollars...
I gave 4,000 dollars in total earlier.
I'll round it up to 1,000 dollars...
and give you 5,000 dollars in total.
- Oh, my. - Since it's for a good cause.
(Dex's list of purchases: Added items, total, 5,000 dollars)
I got it.
- Dex bought the most. - That's right.
Yes. He's our VIP.
- I'm off, now. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Great work.
- Thank you. - I'll send the TV through a truck.
Don't. It'll be tiring.
Gosh, this ended up going to your house.
You're right. I'm carrying this home myself.
Bye.
- Bye. Thank you. - Hyun Moo.
It started with Dex and ended with Dex.
- Bye. - Get home safe.
(The lively Grand Rainbow Bazaar came to an end.)
All right. Let me check the settlement one last time.
That's 540 dollars.
(Seller KUNST begins adding up.)
It looks like they're checking congratulatory money.
And Cha Tae Hyun. Ko Kang Yong. Yerin. Ha Young.
That's 5,350 dollars.
Heo Sung Tae, 3,000 dollars.
- He paid 3,000 dollars? - Yes.
Why? How much is it in total?
He told me he'd pay 1,200 for everything he got.
- He paid more. - He paid 1,800 dollars more.
He paid more since it was for a good cause.
It was so cool that he donated more without saying anything.
- That's right. - Yes.
We didn't know he paid more.
- That's it. - That's it.
Then in total, it's 24,015 dollars.
It's 24,015...
(Total: 24,015 dollars)
You made a lot.
- We spent the day fruitfully. - Seriously.
You're amazing.
(Amazed)
Let's fill up the rest and meet it up to 50,000 dollars.
- Sure. Let's do that. - Okay.
- Let's make it 50,000 neatly. - Yes.
As for the remaining items, I'll discuss with you...
and send them to the places you want.
- Okay. I got it. - I'll send them away.
This is what made me the happiest today.
Both buyers and sellers...
gathered to do a good deed.
We gathered together with that mindset.
Seeing the items that met their owners...
and the owners' big smiles,
- it healed me. - Right. I felt that too.
I was grateful for the people who used their time to come here.
They seemed to have come to have fun with the good deed,
so I was really grateful as someone hosting it.
I received a lot too,
- so I need to share more. - That's right.
My mom told me that.
Living like that, good days will come again.
(Grateful donors who came for the Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
They all look happy when they share.
Exactly. It makes you proud.
(Grand Rainbow Bazaar Guestbook)
(Im Woo Il, Let's Be Happy)
(It's Dazzling When You Share)
That was a good one.
With the sales we made and the money that four sellers...
pitched in made it 5,000 dollars in total.
On top of that, Sung Hwan bought the air.
- He bought the air. - Yes.
- And the painting. - The painting.
- Oh, right. The painting. - I also...
feel so warm-hearted by it.
I'll add 400 dollars more...
- Make it 1,000 dollars? - and make it 1,000 dollars.
- I'll make it 1,000 dollars too. - It's 1,000 dollars?
- With an additional 2,000 dollars, - It's 1,000 dollars each.
We'll donate the total of 52,000 to someplace good.
(The 1st Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
(Total amount donated: 52,000 dollars)
(Next story)
(The Year of the Red Horse is here.)
(Rainbow Club, Run Like a Horse)
(Special)
(He made a good impression with his cold image.)
(He showed a great performance in dramas...)
(like "D.P." Season 2, "Weak Hero Class 2.")
(He even stands out on a musical stage.)
(An all-round skilled actor)
(A multi-talented actor with unexpected charms)
(Actor Bae Na Ra)
(Hello. It's been 16 years since I started living alone.)
(I'm Actor Bae Na Ra.)
(Warmth wraps you up as soon as you enter the house.)
(Things are neatly organized in his house.)
(A house filled with Na Ra's memories)
(A morning with his pet cat, Gureum)
(Shaking)
(Focused on a healthy meal)
(Slurping)
(Actually, this is...)
(my secret tip on daily life.)
(Clean up as soon as you eat.)
(Clean things right away if they get dirty.)
(Satisfied)
(Na Ra's secret tip to keep his place clean)
(The second tip is on health.)
(If you take care of your blood circulation...)
(from time to time, )
(it'll be good for your swelling.)
(Sliding)
(A good tip to stay healthy in a small house)
(I never buy things that are useless.)
(Keeping his muscles with plastic bags)
Go away, sanddust
Come, rain
(Even if it's repeated and gets boring, )
(they all become meaningful for me one day.)
(I Like the Way I Am)
(Dae Ho is waiting for someone.)
(Today's special guest...)
(is Dae Ho's cousins.)
(Dae Ho's big family from Yangpyeong)
(Cousins he's grateful for)
(He wants to give them a day to remember, )
(so he invites them to Seoul.)
(This was Gun Ho's first KTX ride.)
(Thanks to Dae Ho, they got to ride in business class.)
(Thank you, Dae Ho.)
(Their day begins with a cheer.)
(A special minibus for his cousins)
(Yeouido is that way. Mapo-gu is over there.)
(They look around busily...)
(as it's been a while since they last had been in Seoul.)
(I'm sure everyone will like where we're going now.)
Don't tell me we're going...
abroad.
(Incheon International Airport)
(Are we traveling abroad?)
(So the observatory is our first destination?)
(They can't conceal their disappointed look.)
(I must step up my game. They're about to hate this trip.)
(Trying to win them over with a great photo chance)
(Luckily, everyone lightens up.)
(We're just getting started.)
(The highlight of today's tour)
(It's a place beyond imagination.)
(Welcome to Dae Ho's house.)
(They've been waiting for a long time.)
(Your house is so futuristic.)
(I bet Aunt was quite surprised by your house.)
(My cousins...)
(take up 80 percent of my life.)
(Words aren't needed for them to understand Dae Ho.)
"I'm your family."
(You Are Me, and I Am You)